残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 群れのドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で 運命さえまだ知らない 痛い気な瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の体勢 窓辺からやがて取り立つ
ほとばしる 熱いパックスで 想い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
さんの国民のスムープに戻って discuss for aung Score シャコンで欲しい
クリーフiiつため 歌謀な
With a heart that can't be mended, ha-ha-ha.
All right.
Let's do it, ha-ha.
Oh, my gosh.
Did you hear all that gossip?
Asuka, Asuka, Asuka.
They're totally clueless.
Thanks, come again.
At least your pictures don't reveal her personality.
Hello.
Guten Morgen, Chinji.
Guten Morgen.
Hey, why so gloomy?
I'm the most popular girl in school.
You should appreciate your good fortune.
Hey, the other one's here too, isn't she?
Other one?
What are you, stupid?
I'm talking about the first child, of course.
Oh, Ayanami.
Hm?
Hello.
You must be Rei Ayanami, the pilot of the prototype.
I'm Asuka.
Asuka Langley Soryu.
I'm the designated pilot of Ava 2.
Let's be good friends.
What for?
Because it would be convenient.
You know what I mean.
If I'm ordered to, I will do it.
Ooh, freakazoid.
It takes one to know one.
I wonder if only weirdos are chosen to be Ava pilots.
Oh!
You've lost some weight.
Oh?
You're enduring an unrequited love.
Really?
You're so very sure, are you?
Hmm.
A woman with a mole like a tear on her cheek is destined to a life full of heartache and sorrow.
If you're trying to put the moves on me, I'm afraid you can't. Not while that face is pressed against the glass anyway.
It's been quite a while, Kashi.
It's been a while, all right.
You know, you're not as discreet as I remember.
He ain't never been discreet as I remember.
You've finished handing over Unit 2, haven't you?
What are you still doing here?
I received orders this morning that I'll be staying around so, Gorgeous, we can hang around again, just like we used to.
Oh, don't flatter yourself.
Enemy attack?
We've just received this report from the battlecruiser Haruna.
Have detected huge submerged object off the Ki'i Peninsula.
Sending data.
Got it.
The data has been analyzed.
We've just received this report from the battlecruiser Haruna.
Have detected huge submerged object off the Ki'i Peninsula.
Sending data.
Got it.
The data has been analyzed.
The wavelength pattern confirms it.
It's an angel.
All personnel, go to first stage alert.
The recent battle has severely damaged Tokyo-3's intercept system.
Only 26% of our defense capability has been restored.
In addition, our operational capability for actual combat is virtually nil.
Therefore, we're going to have to intercept the target at the water's edge right before it makes land.
Units one and two will mount a coordinated attack in a series of waves.
In other words, close in and take turns.
Roger.
This sucks.
My first fight over Japan and she won't let me handle it solo.
Why do I have to bring you?
S.O.P.
That's just procedures, you know.
Well, let me tell you something first, third child.
Just don't get in my way.
Hmm, his selection as a pilot must have been a joke, right?
Two against one's not what I'd call a fair fight.
It's not fair.
We don't get a choice.
Survivability takes priority.
Huh?
There.
Beginning attack!
I'll handle this angle.
Cover my back, Shinji!
C-Cover you?
Yeah!
Ladies first!
Dammit!
Don't you talk to me like that, you dumb rookie!
In charge!
What?
Well, I'll be damned.
Well, what did you think of that?
A fight should be clean and elegant without waste.
What?
That's a load of bull!
Today at 10.58, 15 seconds AM, Unit 1 was attacked by one of the targets, Alpha, which had separated from the other target, submerged two kilometers off Cerber Mubei.
20 seconds later, Unit 2 was stopped by Target Beta's attack.
I believe the project chairperson summed it up best.
This is pathetic!
This is all your fault!
You totally screwed up my debut battle!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who charged in there acting like an idiot!
Idiot?
How dare you call me that, you pathetic excuse for a combat pilot!
You're just a jerk!
Me?
You were in such a rush to show off, you disregarded procedure!
What was that?!
You look like a drowned rat!
Hmph!
You, you can't say that kind of thing to me!
NERV abandoning operation and transferred command to UN secondary force.
We've been completely humiliated!
At 11.05 AM, the UN forces made an attack with an in-tune mind.
We'll have to redraw the map again.
They succeeded in burning off 28% of the target's structural substance.
Well, it kinda looks dead.
This is merely temporary. The second attack is just a matter of time.
Well, at least we've got time to regroup and you can't ask for more than that.
Alright, you two. Just what do you think your job is?
Piloting Ava?
Wrong! It's to beat the angels!
NERV does not exist to make grotesque public spectacles like this!
Therefore, the two of you will learn to work together!
Why should we?!
Enough!
Why does everyone get so angry here?
Adults have a thing about credibility.
Um, where's Misato?
Clearing things up.
It's the duty of the person in charge to take responsibility for anything that goes wrong.
Oh, look what we have here.
Here are the protests and damage reports from all of the bureaus concerned.
This is a bill from the UN.
And you've got a complaint from public relations as well.
I hope you have fun reading them all.
I already know what they say.
If you're going to fight, please don't do it here, right?
I'd say that was a good guess.
I'll do it after we kill this angel. I will destroy it.
That would be a nice start.
I think you should know that Commander Fuyutsuki isn't exactly happy with this whole situation.
I'm afraid you could be busted back to Lieutenant, or even lower.
I guess it was just good luck within bad luck that Commander Ikari wasn't here.
If he'd been here, you'd have already been fired.
So you've brought me some ideas to help save my job, haven't you, dear friend?
Like this one?
Ah, I thank you, Dr. Ritsugu Akagi.
It's good to have a friend you can count on.
That's nice.
But I'm not the one who'll be saving your backside this time.
This is Mr. Kaji's idea.
Kaji?
I'm home!
Not that anyone's here, of course, but...
What?! What is this?!
Don't be so rude! These are my personal belongings!
You?!
But what in the blazes are you doing in my house?!
Why are you still here?
Still here?!
Don't...
Hmm, yeah, you've been dumped for the new model.
Misato will be living with me.
Of course, that's a much more logical choice when you consider my superior abilities.
Although, honestly, I'd rather live with Kaji.
Say, just why are Japanese houses so small, anyway?
I couldn't even get half my stuff in my new room!
And Japanese sure don't have any sense of privacy.
How can they live in a room without locks?!
Unbelievable!
It's weird.
The Japanese way is to consider the needs of others before one's own.
Misato, how's it going?
You two are going to get along real well.
What?
Just what do you mean?
This is part of your new training.
Say what?!
There is only one way to destroy the seventh angel.
Execute a simultaneous two-point attack on each target's core while the angel is separated.
Oh.
In other words, an attack on both halves by two Evas with perfectly synchronized timing.
Coordination between the two of you will be vital to the success of the mission.
Huh?
To that end, I want the two of you to live together from now on.
No way!
A boy and a girl should never sleep under one roof after the age of seven!
The angel is currently regenerating itself.
It will begin its second assault in six days.
But it's impossible.
We have a way of making it possible.
The master attack pattern will be choreographed using this music.
If you follow it exactly, you will be able to work in sync and completely destroy both targets.
We begin now.
We attack in six days.
I'm getting really worried about Shinji.
He's been gone for three days, hasn't he?
Hey, it's the class rep.
Two of the three stitches.
So, why are you here?
To see on the story he was doing.
What about you?
To look in on Shinji.
Why did you stop here?
Coming.
Hmm?
You betrayed us.
You're dressing alike again, too.
I can't believe this.
Neither can we.
It's all Misada's fault.
We have to eat, breathe and sleep together.
Huh?
You're living in sin.
That's awful.
No, it's not like that.
Ugh.
It's just what is it like?
Hi, everybody.
Would you like to explain all of this to us?
Geez, Shinji.
You should have told us about that part first.
So, how are there coordination drills coming along, Miss Misato?
Not very well, as you can see.
No.
We'll stop.
Not very well, as you can see.
Yes, I can't do.
No, I can't do.
I can't do.
No.
I can't believe this.
Neither can we.
It's all Misada's fault.
We have to eat, breathe and sleep together.
You're living in sin.
That's awful.
No, it's not like that.
It's just what is it like?
Hi, everybody.
Huh?
Um, would you like to explain all of this to us?
Geez, Shinji.
You should have told us about that part first.
I can never seek down the pathetic level this animated turnip lives at.
If you ask me, the whole idea is impossible.
Then you're giving up.
But you don't have anyone else, do you?
Ray?
Yes, ma'am.
Why don't you try?
Well, it looks like I should alter the operation to pair Shinji and Ray.
What?
No!
I can't stand this!
I can't take it anymore!
Wait!
Wait, Asuka!
So even the devil can cry.
Shinji, go!
Go apologize!
Huh?
You made her cry, you jerk!
Go find her and tell her you're sorry!
Um...
Don't say anything.
I know.
I have to pilot the Eva.
I've got no choice.
I'll do it.
No matter what, I'll put Ray and Misato to shame!
But still, you don't have to squash them.
You're being too simplistic, even if you are a male.
I must avenge myself!
My pride!
It's a matter of honor now!
Can't you understand that?
Mmm...
Where's Misato?
At work.
She called earlier.
She'll be there all night.
So, that means we're all alone tonight, huh?
This is the impenetrable wall of Jericho, third child.
What?
Take one step over this wall and you'll be a dead man.
And now it's time to go to bed, children.
Why do Japanese sleep on the floor?
This is so stupid.
Oh, my God.
You're just a child yourself.
No, somebody might see us.
Who's watching?
Somebody.
What?
Forget it, Kashi.
There's nothing between us anymore.
Don't ever do that again, but your lips didn't say no
Tell me which one should I trust your lips or your words?
Oh
Thanks, well looks like you've got troubles
Yeah, a few so is it work or a man or both?
Still in love, huh?
Don't be ridiculous get real who'd want that idiot I
May have been just a kid but getting involved with him was still the stupidest and most idiotic thing
I've ever done in my entire life. I meant that he may still like you did I scare you I'll show you scary
You're only proving my hypothesis
Why don't you just go with your feelings Misato? It's not like it's still eight years ago. You know nothing's changed not a bit
He's still immature
I've got to get to work tomorrow's D-day, you know
The target is broken through the final defense line in Gora
Here it comes. We won't fail this time
Spread your AT fields as soon as the music starts
Then follow the operation choreography. Are you two ready? Roger
Roger
Just remember the moves Shinji full power maximum performance
I know that we'll be finished in 62 seconds. It's coming target entering crowd zero detach external power
Eva launch
Are you
Oh
four
No
So
We'll be right back.
Huh?
Both Ava's are okay.
Oh, jeez!
Pathetic.
What are you doing on my unit, too?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who fell on me!
You're the one who lost time first!
Doobkob!
You're always so slow!
What were you doing staying up so late last night?
Image training for today's battle!
Oh, image training, I'm just that!
Liar!
I know you tried to kiss me while I was sleeping!
You cheat!
You were awake!
Oh, my gosh!
I was just kidding!
Did you really kiss me?
Oh!
No, no!
No, I didn't!
I stopped!
Ava-a-mit!
I can't believe it!
What are you calling for your mother in your sleep and sleepwalking and cause her?
What kind of person...
Those darn kids are embarrassing us again.
I thought they'd be like, don't say, yeah!
They don't want to be so much?
When I come to the end of my mind
The number one, hold my hand
The number one, darling kiss me
Be my sweet soul, and let me see forevermore
You are all I know, but all I want is at the door
Another one, bring me too
Another one, I love you
I love you
When an unhatched angel is discovered in the caldera of the Osama volcano
Especially equipped, Ava must descend into the fires of Hell itself to do battle
Don't miss the next exciting episode, Magma Diver
And don't worry, there'll be lots of man service too